Why is your
Почему у вас
flag as yellow as possible at the bottom and as yellow
флаг максимально снизу жёлтый,
as possible at the top?  Well, it’s very simple,
максимально сверху? Ну, очень просто,
because my country, which holds my
потому что моя страна, у которой мой
passport, the Russian Federation, I am a
паспорт, Российская Федерация, я
citizen of the Russian Federation,
гражданин Российской Федерации,
attacked Ukraine.  I believe that we are
напала на Украину. Я считаю, что мы
responsible for the actions of our
несём ответственность за действие нашей
government and must provide maximum
власти и должны максимально
assistance to Ukraine in order to overthrow
содействовать Украине, чтобы свергнуть
this Putin junta in the Kremlin.
эту путинскую хунту в Кремле.
Hello.
Здравствуйте.
Where are you from?
Вы откуда?
I'm from Novosibirsk.  Where are you from?  Cool.
Я с Новосибирска. Вы откуда? Прикольно.
I am originally from Rostov, but I live in
Я самородом из Ростова, но живу в
Holland.  It's great to move from Rostov.
Голландии. Классно с Ростова переехать.
Move from Bolshie Plyukhi to Maliye Plyukhi.  Uh, what are you talking about?
переехать. Э, о чём вообще?
No, I'm just curious.
Да не, просто мне интересно.
I'm just interested in communicating.  Well,
Мне просто интересно общаться. Ну,
by the way, I won’t even ask why
кстати, даже не буду спрашивать, почему
your
у вас
flag is as yellow as possible at the bottom and as yellow
флаг максимально снизу жёлтый,
as possible at the top.  Well, it’s very simple,
максимально сверху. Ну, очень просто,
because my country, which holds my
потому что моя страна, у которой мой
passport, the Russian Federation, I am a
паспорт, Российская Федерация, я
citizen of the Russian Federation,
гражданин Российской Федерации,
attacked Ukraine.  I believe that we are
напала на Украину. Я считаю, что мы
responsible for the actions of our
несём ответственность за действие нашей
government and must provide maximum
власти и должны максимально
assistance to Ukraine in order to overthrow
содействовать Украине, чтобы свергнуть
this Putin junta in the Kremlin.  I
эту путинскую хунту в Кремле. Я
help in Holland, we have a
помогаю в Голландии у нас вот есть ээ
Russian community here.  We do it,
землячество российское. Мы делаем,
we organize training camps, we make donations
организовываем сборы, делаем ээ донаты
for ZSU.  The guys from Zaporizhzhia make
на ЗСУ. Ребята из Запорожья делают
drones and send them to the front.  So
дроны, передают там на фронт. Так
cool, in short, they beat us up.  By the way, I had
классно, короче, лупят. У меня, кстати,
a classmate, Sanya Prokhorovchk, he
одноклассник Саня Прохоровчк был,
signed up for the zatnik and went to war as some kind of
записался в затнике, пошёл на войну
drone.  I don't I don't know.  Or maybe it was
каким-то дроном. Я не я не знаю. Или это
for my money that someone's drone hit his head,
за мои деньги дроном ему башку раз,
damn it, with someone's drone.  So that's how it is
блин, чьим-то дроном разбило. Так что
.  And what?  Well, it helped in the end.  Well,
так. А что? Ну помогло в итоге. Ну Сане
Prokhor helped Sanya.  Well, what is not, what
Прохором помогло. Ну то, что нет, то что
you are doing, you are basically
вы делаете, вы в принципе правильно
doing the right thing.  It probably helped you.
делаете. Вам же помогло это, наверное.
Well, yes, my conscience clears a little
Ну да, у меня совесть немножко
, because the Russian passport, the fact that
очищается, потому что русский паспорт,
you receive some money
того, что вы получаете деньги какие-то
or you gave up the Russian passport.
или вы от русского паспорта отказались.
Well, do you receive money from someone or
Ну вы деньги от кого-то получаете или
not?  No, I'm Russian, and on the contrary, I'm my own
нет? Нет, я рус я я наоборот свои
money.  And what has cleared your conscience
деньги. А совесть-то у вас от чего
?  Because my Russian
очистилась? От того, что ээ мой русский
passport is being cleansed of blood, which... Do
паспорт очищается от крови, которую А он
you still have a Russian passport?  Yes.   Yes.  I have
у вас есть остался русский паспорт? Да.
I am a citizen of the Russian
Да. У меня У меня Я гражданин Российской
Federation.  Bloody Russian passport?  Yes,
Федерации. Крававый русский паспорт? Да,
I am a citizen of Russia.  I love my country,
я гражданин России. Я люблю свою страну,
but I hate the state.  My country is
но ненавижу государство. У меня страна
good.  How good it sounds.  This
хорошая. Как это хорошо звучит. Это же
sounds beautiful.  I hate my
звучит красиво. Я ненавижу свою своё
state, I love my country.  What do you
государство, люблю свою страну. А чем вы
love about your country?  Well, I'm helping.  It
свою страну любите? Ну я помогаю. Это
sounds very beautiful, doesn't it?  Look, I'm
звучит очень красиво, да? Смотри, я
helping the world get rid of it.  No.  What do you
помогаю миру избавиться. Нет. Чем вы
love about your country?  With your own money.  I
любите свою страну? Своими деньгами. Я
donate euros.  You all love your
жертвую евро. Всем вы любите свою
country.  With the heart.  With the heart.
страну. Сердцем. Сердцем.
Why do you love your country with your heart?
Почему вы любите сердцем свою страну?
Because I was born there.  I am a citizen of
Потому что я родился там. Я гражданин
this country.  I am Russian.  And what are you doing with
этой страны. Я русский. И что вы делаете
your words, hating your country?  I don't I don't
своими словами, ненавидя свою страну? Я
hate.  I love the country.  I
не Я не ненавижу. Я люблю страну. Я
hate the state.
ненавижу государство.
How does a country differ from a state?
А чем страна отличается от государства?
A country is a territory and people, and a
Страна - это территория и люди, а
state is... You love,
государство - это Вот вы любите,
wait a minute, you love your territory, you
погодите, вы любите свою территорию, вы
love Knicksburg.  Okay, yes.  Yes,
любите Книксберг. Так, да. Да,
but you hate Kaliningrad.  No, I
но вы ненавидите Калининград. Нет, я
hate Moscow.  Do you love Moscow? Do you
ненавижу Москву. Вы любите Моск Вы
love Novosibirsk, Knicksburg,
любите Новосибирск, Книксберг,
Vladivostok, but don’t like Moscow?
Владивосток, но не любите Москву?
I hate Moscow.
Ненавижу Москву.
What did you do in Novosibirsk?  I'll
А что вы сделали на Новосибирска? Я
explain.  The thing is, look,
объясню. Дело в том, что смотрите,
Moscow.  Moscow has been taking all its juices
Москва. Москва и Издревли была все соки
from our Rostov since ancient times.  Look,
из нашего Ростова брала. Посмотри,
when do you like what?  I'm talking specifically about your
когда что вы любите? Я именно про вашу
love for Rus'; there was no Moscow.   It's
любовь Руси никакой Москвы не было.
about love.  Let me explain about love
Именно про любовь. Давайте про любовь
.  With all my love, I send
объясню. Я со всей любовью отправляю
my euros to the guys from Zaporizhzhia who
евро свои ребятам из Запорожья, которые
make drones and these.  What does
делают дроны и которые вот этих. А
Russia have to do with this?  Because Russia
Россия здесь при чём? Потому что Россию
has been captured by Putin's government.  No, let's
захватили путинская вла. Нет, давайте мы
just clarify.  You send
просто уточним. Вы отправляетесь с
money from Europe to Ukrainians, earned in Europe
Европы деньги, заработанные в Европе
, so that they can beat your beloved
украинцам, чтобы они били вашу любимую
homeland.  No, not the homeland, but they beat those who
родину. Нет, не родину, а били тех, кто
captured it.  And the country.  Fine.  The one
захватил. И страну. Хорошо. Ту, которую
you love.  No, what are you saying?  No, I am against
вы любите. Нет, ты что? Нет, я против
this, not the one you love.
этого, чтобы не ту, которую вы любите.
Wait, how do you determine, that is, how do
Погодите, а вы определяете, то есть как
they determine?  Let's do it again from the
они определяют? Вы давайте ещё раз с
very beginning, let's do it.  You collect
самого начала, давайте. Вы собираете
money in Europe, then go to
деньги в Европе, так отправляетесь в
Ukraine, and what do you want them to do?
Украину, так и чтобы они долбили что?
Occupiers who are coming from Russia to
Оккупантов, которые идут из России в
Ukraine.
Украину.
That is, me personally, I personally am an
То есть меня лично, вот я лично
occupier, right?  So, you too, huh?  Well,
оккупант, да? Значит, вас тоже, да? Ну,
personally, not a single gift from you arrived to me
ко мне лично ни одного вашего подарка не
.  Why?  You are somewhere far away,
прилетело. Почему? Вы где-то далеко,
like, you are not near Zaporizhzhia.  If near
типа, вы не под Запорожьем. Если под
Zaporizhzhia Novosibirsk, or rather Novosibirsk,
Запорож Новосибирске, коне Новосибирске,
then you are in Novosibirsk.  And those who
то вы себе в Новосибирске. А те, кто
entered the territory of Ukraine are getting what they deserve
прилезли на территорию Украины, вот им
.  These are my quints.  Mine
прилетает. Это мои кинты. Мои и по ним
don't fly very often on them either.  It arrives in quints
тоже не особо прилетают. По кинтам
.  There's Sanya Prokhorov over there.  My
прилетает. Там вон Саня Прохоров. Мой
ken is arriving.  Sanya Prohoroy is a friend.  Sanya
кен прилетает. Саня Прохорой кент. Саня
Prokhoro knocked the drone off his head.  It
Прохоро ему башку дроно. По нему
flies along it.  Sanya Prokhorov is Ukrainian.  It
прилетает. Саня Прохоров украинец. По
flies in from Russia.  He is from
нему с России прилетает. Из он из
Rostov.  You're confusing something.  Wait.
Ростова. Вы путаете что-то. Подожди.
Sanya Prokhoro from classmate.  No, he is my
Саня Прохоро из однокла. Не, он мой
classmate.  Is he just going to get it
одноклассник. Он просто
together or what?  No no.
зада вместе или что? Нет, нет.
Sanya Prokhoro.  Who is he?  Well, let's
Саня Прохоро. Да кто он? Ну давай
see what this is. Tell me your last name
посмотрим, что за Назови свою фамилию,
before Sanya Prokhoro.  Why are you here?  You you you No no no
прежде чем Саню Прохоро. А зачем ты? Ты
, wait, wait.  Do you want to
ты ты Нене не, погоди, погоди. Ты хочешь
record a video so that my parents
записать видео и чтобы моих родителей
can be found in Rostov?  Yes.  I have... And which
нашли в Ростове? Да. У меня А ты какому
prosecutor are you talking to?  Look, my father and
прокурору кото? Смотри, у меня отец и
mother are in Rostov, so you don’t need to
мама в Ростове, так что не надо ты
specifically find their last name and then
специально фамилию, чтобы найти и потом
they apologize.  No, it's not necessary.  You are a
они извинялись. Нет, не надо. Ты
traitor.  You have neither a father nor a mother.
предатель. У тебя нет ни отца, ни мамы.
You have some Prokhorop.  And the one who
У тебя есть Прохороп какой-то. И тот,
most likely likes you is Russian.  And who are you?
который тебя скорее я русский. А ты кто?
What kind of Russian are you?  Russian against Moscow.
Какой ты русский? Русский против Москвы.
Because the Kremlin junta was seized in
Потому что Кремлёвская хунта захватила в
1993 by Yeltsin, who
девяносто третьем году Ельцин, который
shot up the parliament, staged a
расстрелял парламент, сделал
coup d'état, and drafted an
государственный переворот и сдел
illegitimate constitution.  Do you understand?
нелегитимную конституцию. Понимаете?
Fine.  Explain it to me honestly
Хорошо. Объясни мне вот давай так
, as one Russian to another.  Why do
почестно, как русский русскому. Почему у
we in Russia have oil, gas, gold,
нас в России есть нефть, газ, золото,
oil, gas, gold, diamonds, but we live in
нефть, газ, золото, алмазы, а живём
poverty?  Why?  Laundress.  Why?  What?
бедно. Почему? Прачка. Почему? Что?
Because you are a laundress.  Laundresses.  That's why.
Потому что ты прачка. Прачки. Поэтому.
Look, why is little Holland,
Смотри, почему маленькая Голландия, у
which has no oil, gas, gold, or
которой нет нефти, газа, золота,
diamonds, living better than Russia?  Why?
алмазов, живёт лучше России? Почему?
Taker by What else do you need to explain?
Берущий по Что тебе ещё нужно объяснить?
Look, you see, that means you're not Russian.
Смотри, видишь, ты не русский, значит.
Okay, go ahead.  So, you are Russian?   Let's do it
Хорошо, давай. Так, ты русский тебя?
normally.  Now explain to me why
Давай нормально. Вот объясни мне, почему
you live so poorly?
живёшь бедно так?
Why am I a Russian who is against
Почему же я русский, который против
Moscow?  I moved to Holland 18 years ago
Москвы? Я выехал 18 лет назад в
.  I earn money to
Голландию. Я зарабатываю деньги, чтобы
send donations to the Ukrainian armed forces
скидывать донаты на вооружённые силы
, to these Russian occupiers,
Украины, чтобы этих русских оккупантов,
you understand?  I'm not an
понимаешь? Я не
occupier, you understand?  Yes.  All.  And
Я не оккупант, понимаешь? Да. Всё. А
you, I am Russian.
ты Я русский.
How can we bomb them if they smell that
Як их х бомбить, коли вони чують, що
Russia is supporting the ZSU.   Yes.
хтось з России підтримує ЗСУ.
Subscribe to my Telegram right
Да. Підпишись на мій Telegram прям
now.  Axis int.  And the
зараз. Ось вн. А
priest is even more and more important.  YouTube is
попик це дуже и дуже важливо. YouTube
banning us through kargeor
заганяе нас через каргеор в тіньовий
.  And too many videos are not shown to
бан. І дуже багато відео не показуется
people regularly, and information
людям вчасно, не показуется інформація
about the stream is not shown.  Therefore, in order for us to
про стрими. Тому для того, щоб ми мали
quickly sign up immediately
оперативний зв'язок підпишиться прям
.  And the priest there in the telegram is still
зараз. А попик там в телеграмі окмде ще
useful and useful information and we are
теж цікава и корисна інформація и мы
responsible for a permanent operational connection.   It
повинма постійний оперативный зв'язок.
doesn’t matter if YouTube shows you about
Незалежно від того, чи покаже вам про
it.  Glory to Ukraine!  Підписися.
цей YouTube. Слава Україні! Підпишись.